I have the pleasure to present to you,
Dr. Martin Luther King, dear.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
I am happy to join with you today in what will go down in history
as the greatest demonstration for freedom in the history of our nation.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Five score years ago, a great American in whose symbolic shadow we stand today,
signed the Emancipation Proclamation.
This momentous decree came as a great beacon light of hope to millions of Negro slaves
who had been seared in the flames of withering injustice.
It came as a joyous daybreak to end the long night of their captivity.
But one hundred years later, the Negro steel is not free.
One hundred years later, the life of the Negro steel satly crippled
by the manacles of segregation and the chains of discrimination,
one hundred years later, the Negro lives on a lonely island of poverty
in the midst of a vast ocean of material prosperity.